That is what started it all. I've come to say thank you. To you, Inaho.
I understand that once again, I owe you my life.
No. This happens in war.
And how many times does this make it now? Should I start keeping track?
Don't know. And I wouldn't say I've saved you yet.
We are in a war.
You're very kind, aren't you?
You really are.
Tell me something. When this is over, we'll still be friends, won't we?
We will.
I'm very glad.
I am a Salem vs. Lucia.
I am the royal princess, granddaughter of Reyregalia vs. Ravers, Emperor of Verse.
I address the people of Verse.
This war is meaningless and I call for an immediate halt to it.
I am safe, alive and well.
It was not the Terrans who made that attempt on my life.
It was the Orbital Knights who want to invade Earth.
The Terrans are blameless.
Stop the fighting. Stop it now. Immediately.
And make peace with Earth.
I beg you. End this tragedy. Now.
Wait, is that... the Tharsis?
I liberated it from Castle Cruteo.
Because the Count was not worthy of it.
It's all Noah drive is deactivated, which means Count Cruteo is truly dead.
Princess Asalem's location has been pinpointed via laser transmission to the moon base.
And it is controlled by those who share my vision.
Her Highness' heartfelt plea will not reach the ears of anyone.
The final battle will be at the enemy's main stronghold.
Even with the full might of a landing castle, it will not be easy.
My debt to your father has been fully repaid.
You may join my forces if you wish, or flee to the Earth if that's your choice.
Do as you will.
Mars Knight Landing Castle! Vectoring in!
Touchdown point projected to be somewhere within a 20-kilometer radius of UFV headquarters.
Pretty safe bet they're not coming down here with peace in their hearts.
Abandoned surface installations!
All personnel to underground shelters!
I never thought they'd have the nerve to make a direct assault here.
Come on, I thought this world was supposed to be over with now!
Milady, what's...
We are going to do it.
But then I'll keep you going
viol Hundgeh
Giant
This word is a
Get away
How many
Unkind
щit
All
Mills
The
Honey
Thank you.
An act of futility.
Returning fire!
Multiple missile impacts.
Sir, they're bunker busters.
They've broken into the bedrock.
The warheads are penetrating, approaching base complex level.
Now follow me.
Launching sky carrier.
Sir, missile impacts.
18 locations.
Detecting enemy mechanized forces.
Descending now.
All catapract platoons.
All units launch now.
Shire platoon in position.
Follow Bella platoon in position.
Enemy forces closing.
59 seconds to contact.
All units stand by to engage.
Roger.
Here they come.
Annihilate them.
With no mercy.
Enemy catapract assault.
Intercept team casualty rate up to 50%.
50%!
Assault team, advance!
The objective is Princess of Salem!
Locate and terminate on site!
It's dangerous here, m'lady.
We should relocate somewhere safer.
I made it clear that my assassination was a lie.
So why are they still...
Huh? M'lady?
This war was their objective all along.
The assassination plot was just an excuse.
It never mattered one bit whether I had actually been killed or not.
But that is not the case at all, m'lady!
You are the beloved Princess of Salem of the Empire!
Then why are my own people attacking us again right now?!
Huh?
Please forgive me.
Of course.
So...
Why can no one put an end to this folly by the Orbital Knights?
Is there nothing more that I can do to stop it?
I wish I knew!
Okay.
Munitions loading.
70% complete.
A frontal attack against the UFE's headquarters.
Going to be a little hard holding negotiations if what's left of the government has collapsed.
Negotiations not on their agenda.
They invade a territory with brutal force and call it their own.
With no one to denounce them and no international law.
This is a primitive, pure and simple kind of warfare.
If there's something you want, just take it.
Gotten through to the Princess yet?
No, ma'am.
But I have a page out to her security detail leader.
All pilots, remain in your cats.
Stand by to move out on short notice.
Warrant Officer Kaiska!
Is the Dukaili leaving?
Well, not quite sure.
It could turn into a defensive action.
I'm here.
Go for Mustang Leader.
It's for you now.
Mustang 2-2.
I would like to be of assistance with the fight.
In what way, Salem?
All of the major weaponry in Verse is powered by old Noah drives.
Landing castles are no exception to this.
If it's old Noah drive is shut down,
the landing castle will no longer be able to function.
How can we make that happen?
If the person who activated the drive were to somehow lose his life,
then it would shut down automatically.
Like how when the Deucalion came down?
When you suffered your cardiac arrest?
Just like that?
Yes.
And also, someone of the Verse Emperor's bloodline could override it and forcibly shut it down.
In other words, what you're saying is that you can shut it down.
That's right.
Understood.
I'll escort you to the enemy landing castle.
Hey, hold on a damn minute.
Why do you always pull this crap?
What crap?
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
The insane things you say with a perfectly straight face.
Now that we know she's not able to negotiate politically,
her presence here is of no further benefit to us.
But if we can use her tactically, it makes sense to take advantage of that fact.
Besides, don't forget that if we lose, they're just going to kill her anyway.
It's the logical choice.
Logic is the only thing going for it.
How many lives will we lose doing this?
If we don't do it, the same number will die.
Oh, and that's supposed to make it okay?
This is war.
That's exactly my point!
Sorry, Yuki.
But I think we should bet on the method that has the best odds of success.
That's all it is.
I agree with his assessment.
All right, your highness.
I'll run it past the captain.
Thank you very much.
What is it, m'lady?
The royal princess of the First Empire has turned her own people against her.
No, your highness, this is not the will of the Vercian people.
These are just traitors who have hatched a scheme.
No.
The responsibility is mine.
I am the one to blame.
We must hurry.
Message from Lord Sosbone.
Ship located in underground base.
Her highness may be aboard.
All troops proceed at once.
Hey, what are you doing?
That one hasn't been rearmed yet!
Output is stable on the Aldnoah Drive, Captain. We're ready to lift off at your command.
And Princess of Salem?
Currently, she's on level four. She'll arrive momentarily.
Port gun turret number one has been hit!
Enemy approaching.
Engage them.
What cats are prepared?
They're all secured in their racks for transport, Commander.
Send them out!
Right! But it's going to take time.
Princess of Salem?
Currently, she's on level four.
She'll arrive momentarily.
Horde gun turret number one has been hit!
Enemy approaching.
Engage them.
What cats are prepared?
They're all secured in their racks for transport, Commander.
Send them out!
Right, but it's gonna take time!
Princess of Salem.
There is the exit!
Hey, look! Over there!
It's the Deucalion!
Enemy troops on the hull!
Rotate the ship.
Pivot the ship in place.
Don't let more of them aboard.
Deucalion, coming about!
Look, there she is! It's the Princess!
Open the hatch. Get her aboard, now!
In that vehicle, it's Princess of Salem.
Rocket launcher's here!
Target located. Attempting to neutralize.
I repeat, target is located.
And fire!
I'm not scared! I'm not scared! I'm not scared!
You alive?
Keep your foot on the gas.
And I'll cover you.
Raya, it's you!
Come on, now! Come on, come on!
Princess, over here!
Just a little closer now!
Go, your majesty!
What a dollar, it's all!
I'll be all right, m'lady! Go on!
Now seal the hatch.
Aye, aye, ma'am.
Thank you so much, Adele Ritzo.
The Princess is on board and safe!
Deucalion, lift off!
Control, open the gate for us, please.
Come in, Control. Deucalion here.
Please respond.
Captain.
Tubes one through four.
Prepare to fire missiles.
Make your target the main gate.
All tubes open.
Missiles ready.
Standing by.
Now fire!
That ship, it's from the island.
Back it up, and head for the dock.
You go on. I'll try and hold him off.
The mission is as follows.
Several key elements.
After evading fire from the landing,
the Deucalion will go into the stratosphere.
We'll then carry out a cataphract combat drop from above.
That's just insane!
There'll be no cover as we're descending.
We'll be chewed up by AA fire.
I thought of that.
Which is why we first drop unmanned cats as decoys.
The main assault force will be falling through the jumble of decoys,
with the landing castle as their objective.
We're at 20,000 meters.
Commencing revolve!
Scarecrow pods launching now.
You know, it's possible the decoys won't even work.
And we don't know what firepower they've got.
Well, up until now, we've gone blind into battle.
Yeah, but still!
The first objective for the assault team, the anti-aircraft guns.
Then, once their counterattack has been broken,
we bring in Princesses Salem to do her part.
Lieutenant Marito, you'll oversee the assault team selection.
Understood.
It's best if I deploy in the first wave.
Now?
Yuki, I probably have more experience facing Martian weapons than anyone on Earth.
Overhead! Multiple radar returns!
Anti-air warfare, intercepting now!
Decoid cataphracts hit!
Chaff and flares now being deployed!
Assault team, it's go time!
Mustang leader to all units!
Laser comms will be poor due to the blizzard,
and radio jamming will get stronger the closer we are to the castle.
Remember our briefing information, and fight accordingly!
Mustang 1-1, copy!
Mustang 2-2, copy!
Mustang 3-3, copy!
Mustang 4-4, copy!
Let's go!
Please don't let them hit me!
When you're that scared, you're more likely to get hit.
Huh?
Bullets like to go looking for cowards.
Just be confident, and the bullets will run from you.
Mustang 3-3!
Use my orange color to guide you in.
No!
That's too fast!
I'll drop in using the decoys as a shield.
After the objective leaves the clouds,
I'll fall until the last second and decelerate.
Objective sighted!
Incoming enemy cataphract!
Mustang 2-2, drop zone secured!
Mustang 2-2, I have eyes on you. Approaching.
Don't do anything stupid.
I thinned out their anti-aircraft guns to make it easier for stragglers.
Wait just one second here. Are you saying you did that to help me?
This isn't right. Communications are way too clear.
I apologize for the poor accommodations, Princess.
This is fine.
Control to Princess 1. Proceed to drop position.
Roger that. Princess 1 heading for drop.
I'm getting wild and loud. Tell me I'm still in your room.
I'm going for you, but I'm still in your room.
Princess 1, you protect that passenger.
No matter what, you guard her with your very life.
Princess 1, prepare for drop.
Princess 1, ready for drop.
Princess 1, go for drop.
Princess 1, go for...
Huh?
We're being attacked!
What happened?
This can't be.
There's nothing on the radar.
Anti-air teams!
Protect the Deucalion!
The Deucalion.
So they transplanted the Aldnoa from that cataphract.
But with my Orlaine dead, they could not activate it.
So then, it must have been Princess Asalem who brought it back to a state of operation.
That infernal ship.
Mustang 4-4!
Son of a bitch!
Get me a damage report!
Starboard side!
Empty gravity devices!
Two through seven, completely offline!
We're losing altitude!
We route all our energy into propulsion.
Then set a course for...
The landing castle.
We'll flatten that damn thing with this ship.
Where is Salem?
Haven't gotten the signal yet!
Huh?
Warcraft for Kaizuka!
Three o'clock!
That can't be.
No!
It's the Deucalion!
All units, scatter!
Bizarre!
Ain't just what I could say about humans.
The maisil الطifor.
I felt found that I could believe that my processing strength was deemed sadece committingente File嘛.
For if there's no place for a consequence, it shows all sorts of nature, and it shows all the time that the cop 가운데 finds itself.
I say cry yeah
I say lie yeah
I say rise yeah
I say get the sky no step to step
I say ah ah ah ah
I say truth and right but this night
Let them back see that
Signals it you that
Let them diffuse my house and come and build it
Let them back see that
Signals it you that
Let them the you
exploring
women
bun